A parcel for you, Bridget.
Argentina? Who from? What does it say?
'We was...' We were penpals.
Nice muscles.
You mean our milk
you borrowed three weeks ago.
I forget nothing!
Tough guy, eh?
Why don't I show you how to do it properly?
Fascinating.
-  Here's a cushion.
-  Oh, thank you.
Oh, my goodness. What are we going to do?
But those clothes!
He is so old- fashioned.
Room service.
I pulled, you come. You are the butler.
The butler?
Yeah? Can you cycle 50 kilometres?
-  Oh, please, Nick. You have a spare room.
-  No way. Not my problem.
I don't care.
It's like this.
Go on, then, tell him.
Hector, is this you?
-  Servants.
-  Yeah, my servants.
-  Shut up, Nick.
-  Hector will stay with us, won't you, Hector?
-  It's the landlady!
-  The tarantula!
The flatmates go shopping for Hector.